

# Prince Ekpenyong



#### Address

45 Martins street Lagos 245105

**Phone Number** 08061325196

Email Address prinzana@mail.com

Twitter @prinzanah

#### **CERTIFICATIONS**

Initiation & Project Planning
Udemv

Introduction to Project Management

Udemy

**Time Management for Personal** Udemy

Professional Productivity Grammar

Udemy

**Business Data Analysis** Udemv

Time & Task Management
Udemy

**Super human Productivity**Udemv

Master Difficult Conversation
Udemy

Write Like a Boss: Master Business Writing Skills Udemy

Write Better Emails: Tactics for Smarter Communications Udemy

**Emotional Intelligence at work** Udemy

**Innovation Masterclass** Udemy

**Procurement Masterclass** Udemy

#### **FUN THINGS I DO**

Reading
Scrabble
Brain-storming
Chess

#### **CAREER SUMMARY**

I have kept maintenance operations efficiently and smoothly by delivering successful leadership and team management at all levels. I am experienced in supervising, overseeing the organizational needs and solving routine, corrective and preventive maintenance from simple to complex problems. With more than 3 years of experience in the field of Facility Management. I have proven construction techniques, efficient scheduling practices, and error free compliance inspections. As an Electrical Engineer, I have a well-rounded background in power systems management and refined talents in analytical and problem-solving skills as well as decision- making skills, which made me an ideal fit for the Facility Manager position. Additionally, I am a proven expert in delegation and a consistent collaborator. My present/previous roles have strengthened my abilities in communication and leadership, including focused attention to details and accuracy.

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### **Softcom Nigeria Limited**

(June 2019 - Present)

Facility Manager

Prepared and administered preventative maintenance work orders.

Read work orders to prepare for equipment setup.

Performed preventative maintenance on electrical panels and distribution systems,

Saving the establishment 30% off future repair spending.

Responded to emergencies and outages that required additional labour and assistance for repairs.

Provided facility inspection and maintenance to ensure superior levels of cleanliness and upkeep.

Track inventories and material availability and place order when necessary Tracked and documented operational and financial records to perform analysis of performance and costs.

Documents and track all financial expenses using Microsoft Excel sheets. Managed a team comprising of; Plumbers, Cleaners, Electricians, Heating Ventilation and Air Condition, IT personnel and Securities.

### **WorkStation Nigeria Limited**

(August 2016 - April 2019)

Facility Manager

Have scheduled routine maintenance and repair of facility equipment such as Air

Conditioner and Generator sets.

Managed staff of 12, created work schedules, distributed assignments and supervised day-to-day operations

Monitored inventory and ordered supplies while adhering to the maintenance budget

restrictions

Instructed team members in ground keeping practices, including lawn cultivation,

pruning and grounds design

Managed supply inventory and assigned replenishment to team members Communicated with clients to provide price quotes, discuss design needs and schedule work

Monitored over [Number] workers to complete projects on time and under budget

with both client and employee satisfaction

#### **EDUCATION**

## Cross River University of Technology Bachelors Electrical/Electronics Engineering

(June 2009 - July 2014)

#### **SKILLS**

**Organizational Skills** 

Expert

**Negotiation Skills** 

Intermediate

**HVAC Systems** 

Intermediate

**Team Player** 

Advanced

**Interpersonal Skills** 

Intermediate

Leadership Skills

Advanced

**Time Management** 

Intermediate

**Supervisory Skills** 

Advanced

**Budgeting/Accounting Skills** 

Intermediate

Written/Communication Skills

Advanced